Sometimes they don't come back alone.
White Noise 2: The Light is a thriller, horror,
fantasy film directed by Patrick Lussier.
A man's family brought back from the verge of death, he then
discovers he can identify people who are about to die.
Abe Dale, played by Nathan Fillion.
Sherry Clarke, played by Katee Sackhoff.
Henry Caine, played by Craig Fairbrass.
Marty Bloom, played by Adrian Holmes.
Julia Caine, played by Teryl Rothery.
Dr. Karros, played by William MacDonald.
White Noise: The Light, also marketed as White Noise 2, is a 2007 supernatural horror thriller
film directed by Patrick Lussier and starring Nathan Fillion and Katee Sackhoff.
Written by Matt Venne, it is a stand-alone sequel to the 2005
film White Noise, directed by Geoffrey Sax.
The film received a theatrical release internationally on January 5, 2007, but was
released direct-to-video in the United States on January 8, 2008.
The film received generally positive reviews, but was not commercially
successful, and failed to recoup its $10 million budget.
The film explores themes of suicide, murder, near-death
experience, delayed death, save people.
The tone is dark and intense.